Ivy Wang

User Experience & Interface Designer

About

Hello, I am ready to design something amazing! I love to learn from research, and craft meaningful decisions that blend into useful solutions. I feel proud being able to bring helpful products to people and see their smiles.

Professional Skills

Software & Tools

Design Skills

Figma Adobe Suite Design Thinking User Research

Sketch Canva

Rapid Design **User Testing**

Unity

Wire-framing Interface Design

HTML+CSS

Interaction Design

Soft Skills

Videography

Fast Learning Rapid Thinking Task Management

Problem Solving Critical Thinking

Education

Simon Fraser University

Bachelor of Arts - Interactive Arts and Technology Concentration in Design

September 2015 - December 2020

Language

English Working proficiency

Mandarin Native tongue Contact: wangivy1108@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://ivywang1108.github.io/ivyportfolio/

Experiences

UX/UI Designer - AutoMetrics

Took ownership of the entire design process. Redesigned the user interface of a product that monitors welding operation quality, made decisions on the core features and provided users with brand new user-friendly and reliable monitor experience.

Conducted user research to understand current user pain points, developed new product goals and design directions based on user feedback and did competitive analysis to understand industry trends.

Created marketing videos and brochures that highlighted the company's core features and main services. Also updated the company's website with new product design following company's brand guideline.

September 2021 - March 2022

Graphic/UX Design Volunteer - Build a Biz Kids

Maintained the company brand style, designed multiple-day curricula for facilitators that were easy-to-follow, which later became a template for future courses.

Worked with a company(YouMoveMe) to re-design their Franchise Opportunity Webpage.

Worked with another designer to re-design the company founder's personal webpage which became more engaging and organized.

Designed logo for the company's stock game for kids. Did sketches, and iterations following company brand style while keeping kids as users in mind.

Feburary 2021 - April 2022

Interests •

Interface Design	Victual	Movies
Photography	Travel	Lego